oh sweet thank you so much this birthday
party is magnificent
you have no idea how much this [ __ ]
means to me and this cake - it's so pink
and cute I can't believe you and dr.
Robotnik did this all for me that must
be the happiest Dingo in the whole wide
world how can I ever make it up to you
up in this [ __ ] hey buddy don't worry
about it this is your special day hey
why don't you have some cake Robotnik
isn't here yet but I don't see why that
should stop you from having the time of
your life boy oh boy
doesn't look damn good I might just take
you up on that offer my friend in fact
it looks so good I might just shove it
up my ass ha ha just kidding
time to dig in so how's it taste I got
it from Eric Queen this strawberry
frosting it's it's sugar-free what the
[ __ ] this whole birthday is ruined
ruined I say hey sugar free cake at a
birthday party is almost done here of
don't you start this with meat and go
when we went to Dairy Queen you said you
wanted sugar free no I didn't peepee
that's a flat-out lie and you know it
[ __ ] you didn't even go into the
bathroom when we were there [ __ ] I
pooped in my pants you know what I'm not
arguing over this do you realize how
much this cake cost me two dollars in 86
cents that's right and I could have
gotten myself two egg rolls for that a
quick trip what's with that look
say something you ungrateful piece of
ass I'm not talking to you you think I
give a [ __ ] my mother [ __ ] Sleet
[ __ ] I don't give a [ __ ] what you do oh
my God what the hell is that
Dingo Dingo behind you the cake is
floating yeah right that's a load of
[ __ ] do you really think I'm stupid
enough to believe that cakes don't even
have wings
dink oh I'm serious it's coming right
for you
helped me Sleet this cake is trying to
rape me don't move then go I've got this
what are you waiting for Sleet shoot it
shoot it now before it's too late
I can't there's there's nothing there
it's a ghost or some [ __ ]
gave their boys hope you didn't start
the party without me what is this what's
going on your roundness get out of here
there's something wrong with that
birthday cake
dr. Robotnik runs from nobody especially
not a birthday cake Robotnik run away
that cake is being possessed by a cake
or some [ __ ]
it'll [ __ ] you in the ass you dumb [ __ ]
that's not a ghost that's a killer robot
that I built last weekend it is designed
to immediately attack the sexiest person
in the room I was going to use it
against Bart Libby but you're ruined if
you fools
calculation why stars not sexy
calculation nine stars very sexy
[Music]
calculation ten stars super sexy threat
detected
[Music]